{
    "subject": "resource/Children's_Hospital_for_Wales",
    "predicate": "property/region",
    "object": "resource/Cardiff",
    "human_readable": "Children's Hospital for Wales is located in Cardiff.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9863017797470093,
            "question": "Is there a children's hospital in Cardiff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9836177825927734,
            "question": "Where is the Children's Hospital for Wales located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9281831979751587,
            "question": "What city is home to the Children's Hospital for Wales?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9020997881889343,
            "question": "What is the name of the hospital in Cardiff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8966597318649292,
            "question": "Can you name a hospital in Cardiff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8868805766105652,
            "question": "Where would you go for pediatric care in Cardiff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8289251327514648,
            "question": "What Welsh city houses a major children's hospital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8095428943634033,
            "question": "If you needed pediatric care in Wales, where would you likely go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.594115674495697,
            "question": "In which city is a prominent children's hospital situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41978949308395386,
            "question": "Name a hospital known for treating children."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Children's Hospital for Wales is located in Cardiff.",
            "html": "dbpedia_858_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which city is a prominent children's hospital situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_858_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you needed pediatric care in Wales, where would you likely go?",
            "html": "dbpedia_858_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What Welsh city houses a major children's hospital?",
            "html": "dbpedia_858_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_858_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_858_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_858_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_858_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_858_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_858_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_858_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_858_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_858_98.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_858_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of evidence that support this triple:\n\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_858/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt mentions the construction of The Children's Hospital for Wales in Cardiff.\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_858/re-ranker-msmarco/100.txt lists the address of Noah's Ark Children's Hospital For Wales as being located on the Heath Park campus, which is also home to the University Hospital of Wales in Cardiff.\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_858/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt explicitly states that The new Noah\u2019s Ark Children\u2019s Hospital for Wales (CHfW) is based on the site of the University Hospital of Wales in Cardiff."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention the Children\u2019s Hospital for Wales and Noah's Ark Children's Hospital For Wales, both of which are stated to be based or located in Cardiff. Therefore, the statement that the Children's Hospital for Wales is located in Cardiff is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}